export const questionsAndAnswers = [
    {
      question: "123 + 184",
      answer: 307,
    },
    {
      question: "214 + 107",
      answer: 321,
    },
    {
      question: "214 + 243",
      answer: 457,
    },
    {
      question: "248 + 354",
      answer: 602,
    },
    {
      question: "352 + 124",
      answer: 476,
    },
    {
      question: "286 + 408",
      answer: 694,
    },
    {
      question: "385 + 426",
      answer: 811,
    },
    {
      question: "252 + 464",
      answer: 716,
    },
    {
      question: "105 + 484",
      answer: 589,
    },
    {
      question: "314 + 529",
      answer: 843,
    },
  ];
